<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Projects>
  <Project>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Title>Infotrack</Title>
    <Path01>../../Image/Project/Infotrack/Thumb/01.jpg</Path01>
    <Path02>../../Image/Project/Infotrack/Thumb/02.jpg</Path02>
    <Path03>../../Image/Project/Infotrack/Thumb/03.jpg</Path03>
    <Path04>../../Image/Project/Infotrack/Thumb/04.jpg</Path04>
    <Description>
      Technologies used : ASP.NET 3.5, 4.0, C#, ASP.NET MVC4, Entity Framework 4.5, Telerik Frameworks, LINQ,
      XML, XSLT, XSD, AJAX, WCF,HTML5, CSS3[image sprites and other forms element styling] , XHTML, DHTML, Razor, SQL SERVER 2008, JQuery, ABCPdf,  MVVM
      and Module Pattern Javascript, KnockoutJS. TFS(Team Foundation Server), Dependency Injection[IInject], MS Unit Test, WinMerge etc.

      <p>Development Methodology : Agile Methodologies(SCRUM) was used</p>

      <p>
        Back-End Development Involved : Optimized and used best practises such as using Dependency Injection and better OOP approach such as Pablos SOLID Principles with vastly used design pattern such as
        MVC, Factory Pattern, Facade pattern of the existing code. Modified and fixed exisitng stored procedure and used LINQ for any new queries. Mapped and auto-filled records for existing users.
        worked on Integration between Command Point,which is a Desktop[Winform] Application, to web application[Infortrack]. Modified and added new features in WinForm application[CommandPoint] as well. Worked on Delivery System made of WCF and these are mainly used to get information
        from Government Online Resources. Samples are available in the image gallery. Created and modified variety of certificates those will be generated on the fly when client orders for them. I have
        used ABCPDF to generate those certificates. I have also implemented advanced search option.
      </p>

      <p>
        front-End Development Involved:  Branding core product[Infotrack] using best approach of the latest technologies and JavaScript design pattern[MVVM - KnockoutJS, Module Pattern]. Image sprites,
        Slicing and resizing images, choosing colors and design to have better look and feel of the core products as well as all the retailers such as www.superfastcomputersearch.com.au, www.sydneylegalagents.com.au, www.service1st.com.au etc.
      </p>

      <p>
        Features and Maintenance: Migrated asp.net 3.5 to asp.net 4 (MVC 4) of some of the projects. Pricing and Payment mechanism [ePAY],  Modification and bug fixed
        for Pre-Purchase Reports, NSW Property Certificates, eNOS, WA Landgate title search,
        Vic title alert, CRR Search, Property Enquiries, NSW LPI etc. Beside development, I used to do 3rd level help desk support and liaise with client directly on the issues and change requests.
      </p>
    </Description>
  </Project>
  <Project>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Title>Kaplan Australia</Title>
    <Path01>../../Image/Project/Kaplan/Thumb/01.jpg</Path01>
    <Path02>../../Image/Project/Kaplan/Thumb/02.jpg</Path02>
    <Path03>../../Image/Project/Kaplan/Thumb/03.jpg</Path03>
    <Path04>../../Image/Project/Kaplan/Thumb/04.jpg</Path04>
    <Description>
      Technologies used: ASP.NET 4.0, C#, 3 Tier Architecture, Component Art Framework, LINQ, XML, XSLT, Web Services, ASP.NET Web API for Single Sign On and Integration, AJAX, JQuery,
      XHTML, CSS, twitter Bootstrap, SQL Server 2008, TortoiseSVN, WinMerge, Classic ASP, Crystal Report 8, Onyx CRM etc 
      
      <p>Development Methodology : Agile Methodologies(SCRUM) was used</p>
      
      

  </Description>
  </Project>
  <Project>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Title>Bond International</Title>
    <Path01>../../Image/Project/Bond/Thumb/01.jpg</Path01>
    <Path02>../../Image/Project/Bond/Thumb/02.jpg</Path02>
    <Path03>../../Image/Project/Bond/Thumb/03.jpg</Path03>
    <Path04>../../Image/Project/Bond/Thumb/04.jpg</Path04>
    <Description>
      Bond International Software provide software solutions for recruitment consultancies and corporations.

      I was assigned to develop their core product using cutting-edge technologies. The technologies I have used
      are ASP.NET 4.0, c#, LINQ, XML, XSLT, AJAX, Web Services, XHTML, CSS, JQuery, SQL Server 2005 and 2008,
      Javascript, Crystal Report 2010, CRM(ADAPT), Business Object Explorer, Query Explorer, Screen Design Tools, Classic ASP,
      Java(JSP).

      Core product[e-recruitment] development involved Candidate Registration, Job listing and Searching, CV upload mechanism,
      extracting  CV to the corresponding fields, Front-end look and feel, timesheet management etc. This core product
      was embedded to all the client's portal and did necessary modification based on each of the clients requirements,
      sometimes I have even added new features which are specific to some clients requirements. I have also branded this
      core product based on the client's portal look and feel.



    </Description>
  </Project>

  <Project>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Title>LoveID</Title>
    <Path01>../../Image/Project/LoveID/Thumb/01.jpg</Path01>
    <Path02>../../Image/Project/LoveID/Thumb/02.jpg</Path02>
    <Path03>../../Image/Project/LoveID/Thumb/03.jpg</Path03>
    <Path04>../../Image/Project/LoveID/Thumb/04.jpg</Path04>
    <Description>
      To develop this website I have used ASP.NET 3.5 using  C# , XML, XSL,AJAX, Web services,
      DHTML, HTML, CSS, SQL Server-2008, JavaScript, JQuery. o	Task included Creating Shopping Cart
      and Implementing Payment System for it, Member Profile and Recurring Billing Cycle in Express
      Checkout for subscription, Point Based Payment System,  Role Based Membership, Custom Content
      Management System, QR(Quick Response) Code generation for mobile device, Creating, Resizing,
      Cropping images  and printing in PDF file, E-mail Notification, Creating Pie Chart of Online User
      Statistics and frequent use of some features and generating CSV(Comma Separated Value) file to
      download the report as well, Using LINQ to SQL Classes, Stored Procedures, Invoicing, Using JQuery
      to have some controls in Front End such as accordion, T-SQL in SQL Server 2008.
    </Description>
  </Project>
  <Project>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Title>Shakespeare</Title>
    <Path01>../../Image/Project/shakespeare/Thumb/01.jpg</Path01>
    <Path02>../../Image/Project/shakespeare/Thumb/02.jpg</Path02>
    <Path03>../../Image/Project/shakespeare/Thumb/03.jpg</Path03>
    <Path04>../../Image/Project/shakespeare/Thumb/04.jpg</Path04>
    <Description>
      This digital Ad I have created using Action Script 2.0, PHP, HTML, CSS, Flash, Photoshop, Illustrator,
      Javascript. This was done for one of the real estate in Melboure called Shakespearegrove.
    </Description>
  </Project>

</Projects>
